Get indoors as quickly as you can!
Th-Thank you!
Wh-What in the world?
What are these creatures?
Galilea.
Yeah. Looks like it's starting.
This is a lot worse than
our worst case scenario.
Nah.
It's actually precisely as expected...
as far as Prince Lloyd is concerned.
I Was Reincarnated as the 7th Prince
so I Can Take My Time
Perfecting My Magical Ability 2nd Season
Days Ago
Saria...
Can I be a part of your recital?
I'd love to sing a song here in the church!
That's an odd, heart-warming
thing to bring up at random.
We were in the middle of discussing the very
important business of protecting His Holiness...
It'll be okay!
There won't be an attack
or an assassination.
And since I can't do anything
to help with guarding people...
True.
It might be safest for Lloyd
to be in the Daen Cathedral.
I'd love to sing with you!
But that calls for rehearsal.
I'll help as well.
So, what were you trying to
pull with that nonsense, boss?
Well...
I think that the pope himself
might be the mastermind.
What are you basing that on?!
The most fundamental of
deductions, my dear Jihriel.
He probably has a ton of
spare time on his hands!
And you need a ton of time and
money to build a shop like that!
I'm bored!
Let's make
chimeras!
That really is pretty elementary!
Which is why,
during the Great Advent Festival,
I'll be waiting here for the trouble to start.
You guys should probably
rest up while you can.
Practice!
Episode 20: Invasion
Rumble Rumble Rumble
Yeah. Prince Lloyd will do something
about whoever's behind all this.
We have to protect the city!
And how, exactly, are you a mere prince?
He was able to cut through
Prince Lloyd's Luxa!
I'm more impressed by how he seems
fine after that ass kicking!
Come on, Jihriel!
The sooner we get rid of the chimeras,
the sooner we can back up Prince Lloyd!
But...
He's so fiercely strong.
Could Prince Lloyd really need our help?
It stands to reason he'd be fierce.
He's been pissed off all this time...
over what happened before...
and most recently.
People represent the potential
of magic to Prince Lloyd,
and after seeing what's been
done right under his nose...
he's gonna be furious.
That sounds like less reason to worry—
It's the other way around!
This pope, Guitane,
represents that potential too!
Look, we need to kill the
chimeras and get back, fast!
That attack has made something clear to me.
I no longer care about Charles or Jihriel.
God.
You are a god, and by killing you,
I will fully descend into my abyss.
If that's what you wanna believe, sure.
You're wrong, though.
Bring it.
Those are Crow's crows.
And the signal...?
Three caws...
The pope's the mastermind!
This is awful! But...
it's as Lloyd predicted.
Take shelter inside of the cathedral!
That doesn't confirm that the other
bishops are all innocent, though.
Some of them might be working in tandem.
Archbishop Dante...
Those stitches...
are suspicious
because they remind me of the chimeras!
Purification!
Thank you...
Um... you're Archbishop...?
Miss, you're so adorable!
I'm gonna keep you nice and safe—
Poison Punch!!
Poison Punch!
Shoot! He was so creepy I
just reacted on reflex!
Very nice. I'm never
washing this cheek again.
You really should! There's poison on it!
Wh-What is going on here?
Bishop Anastasia?
Good grief. I had hoped to lop off
your head during the chaos...
Isn't it unbecoming of a bishop to
carry those kind of things around?
The Pope's Forces
Lunar Priestess Anastasia
It is. Which is why I'll be
tendering my resignation.
I was right, then.
The one in the middle...
He clearly has a bizarre amount of mana.
I am Grimoire. the Forbidden Tome!
The Pope's Forces, A-Rank Chimera
Grimoire (?) the Forbidden Tome
It... It can't be!
Grimoire? As in...
You fool! Haven't you heard of him?!
This is the problem with kids these days!
He's the legendary demon who wreaked
havoc upon the Saloum Kingdom
in days long gone by,
before being sealed away!
When I was a child, parents used to scold
their children by saying that Grimoire
would come for them if they misbehaved!
But now the seal has been broken?!
Grimoire will come for you...
...if you misbehave?
Here I am.
I am no other! And now, in this kingdom
that had the nerve to imprison me...
I will have my revenge!
Why grey?!
Hey, Mumbles! I don't mind
acting as a distraction,
but what the hell are we
supposed to do next?!
I wonder if the church
will be okay without us.
Pay attention!
The church has that old bag, Melissa,
to look after it. It'll be fine!
She might not look like much,
but she's pretty great at what she does,
You needn't worry.
with magic and everything.
She's not impressive as me,
the great Batts, though!
Pay attention, damn it!
The messenger crows are
behaving strangely, too.
Especially the ones toward
the center of town.
There's something else going on here.
That dude can really move.
You might be the second
prince's goons, or whatever,
but that don't mean I trust any of you...
The Pope's Forces, SS-Rank Chimera
Nether-Beast, Black Dragon Chimera
Whoa. Whoa!
What the hell is that thing?!
Mumbles, what are we gonna—
Is he serious?
He's going up against that monster?
Without even hesitating?
Batts, men shouldn't run
their mouths so much.
It's all about communicating with your back.
I get you now, Dante.
Just now I could hear that quiet bastard's
kick-ass, rocking shout!
Looks like I'm taking another step
towards becoming a great bishop!
Aomaki
Akamaki
In that instant, time was scattered like
the petals of a flower in the wind,
moving every so slowly...
giving the foe who defies me a chance
to reflect on their entire life.
A vision playing out at
five centimeters per second...
But realistically...
a vertical drop at the speed of sound
where you can't break your fall!
Akamaki
Aomaki
Did that sate you?
Your fleeting life, so much like
falling cherry blossoms...
because my Rakkaken is a one-hit kill!
The Pope's Forces, A-Rank Chimera
Shakra, Falling Flowers Fist
Wh-What just happened?!
Even through the eyes of
a martial arts layman...
Bunhead's offense was truly incredible.
As impossible as it seemed, she was
able to restrain those six arms,
and it looked like they melded together...
Before Bunhead was slammed into the ground!
Bunhead!
Hey! Are you okay over there?!
It's pointless.
As I told you, my Rakkaken
kills with a single blow.
Are you worms trying to
make me repeat myself?
Why do the two of you have
the same face, anyway?
It's because we're, well, twins...
Gulp
That's making this twice as tiresome.
So irritating...
I'll kill you both at once!
Bunhead!
Impossible! You should be dead!
Without being able to break your fall,
your brain should be all over—
I did break my fall, though.
At the last second.
I happened to stumble upon
a delicate-looking arm...
So I ripped it off,
and made a cushion out of it.
You'd have been better off
watching your life flash before you.
Y'know, my life really
did flash before my eyes.
And it reminded me of something...
The Rakkaken—the Falling Flower Fist—
A phantom style of martial arts that
vanished in a single generation,
with no other disciples...
I guess the wraith of Shakra, the founder of
the Rakkaken form, is inside that chimera.
My Rakkaken was perfected
after I gained this chimera body!
Superhuman reflexes afforded by six
eyes that no human could have!
Grappling techniques made
possible with six arms!
Instant throws that don't allow
for breaking of the fall!
And you dare to—
Why exactly do you want to be strong?
Bunhead...
Millions of times...
I punched, and punched, and trained
myself to the point of tears.
And why did I do it? For the sake of others?
I did it to be popular.
Madness.
You dare stick your neck into
this sacred battle for such a—
What about you?
Look what it's done to your face...
Are you telling me it was for no reason?
There is no way I'll lose to you,
not after you've cast aside your humanity!
Her beliefs...
Her qi techniques... Her stance...
I knew it...
The Hundred Flowers Fist!
I don't know if I should
thank or curse the gods.
To run across you again...
Warrior
Shakra...
If you fail a hundred times,
then simply try a million times more.
It's illogical.
Don't let a single loss discourage you.
I am too logical for that!
I chose to be chimera instead of a human!
To have an unaging, superhuman body!
That is clearly the logical choice!
And she says I've thrown something away?
A little girl who's been barely
alive for a few years? Unacceptable.
Imbecile. Is she gonna charge
straight at me again?
The sheer stupidity...
I will strike her down.
Idiot.
I will end you.
It felt like revenge,
as my field of vision was obscured as if
a flower petal blown right across my eyes,
ever so fluidly...
Rakkaken
Please! You must inherit my techniques!
If you don't, the Rakkaken will die out!
Didn't you lose to Hyakkaken?
Give up your school, old man.
It's over.
To hell with your hundred efforts...
your million efforts!
One loss was enough to
bring it all to an end!
I curse you.
It hurts. I'm so angry. And desperate.
Desperate for the power
to kill in an instant...
Come along with me. I'll prepare
a wonderful body for you.
To what end?
For the sake of others?
I did it to be popular.
The impact of the blow was so powerful
it forced my consciousness
back into the present.
A hundred flowering fists,
flying as fiercely as the winds of a storm.
But... Rakkaken will not fall!
Will not be defeated!
Rakkaken
Great work, Bunhead!
You see that, you monster?! Now that
it's over, you didn't amount to...
No.
It obviously wasn't an easy victory!
Tearing limbs off,
every time she was grabbed...
Over and over again!
Every time!
She literally tore victory
from the hands of defeat!
Against a monster that was a haphazard
mish-mash of stolen strengths...
Her diligence won the day!
This was a victory... for the human body!
How's... that...?
Do you see...?
The strength of... my Rakkaken...
She's still alive?!
Let's purify her to end it.
Yeah. I saw it.
Pretty impressive!
You're still trying to throw me.
You win. Those were some amazing grapples.
And you never gave up.
It was very human... and very handsome!
I see...
I see, now.
All I really longed for... was someone
to recognize what I'd accomplished.
Pyrlanse Incinis!
Wahh!
Galilea! My power isn't
working on them at all!
Makes sense!
They're basically meat puppets,
and probably aren't too sensitive to pain!
Plus, the goathead is one of those
pains in the ass that
regenerates itself with mana!
Its sorcery is potent, as well!
How can we fight it?!
You two bishops, keep the church safe.
Talia, back me up with divine sorcery!
I'll look for an opening and then
restrain them with my webs!
Restrain me?
You think that's really going to work
against I, Grimoire the Forbidden Tome?!
Oh, knock it off! We know you're a phony!
Hang on, Talia.
What is it?
Is it possible our guy is the phony?
What are you saying, Galilea?!
Grim's so much more...
Hey!
I picked up some pancakes for you guys.
He fell asleep.
He sure did.
...way more... cute.
Yeah.
Then... is he the real deal?
Behold!
The power of the ancient sorcery wielded
by Grimoire, the Forbidden Tome!
Smash
D... Don't tell me?
Arctis Obscura.
What the hell?
Not even a demon on the inside.
Here.
You two purify that clown.
Galilea, you're gonna focus on plugging
the various holes around town.
R-Right!
So, who were you, anyway?
Well, I was actually a sorcerer who studied
ancient magic when I was alive...
Heh heh heh...
And that was how I became
a fan of Mr. Grimoire!
Purify.
So, you think that was...?
Could it be...?
My Rakkaken will live on! It will never die!
It's yours now, Hyakkaken girl.
Next time, on Episode 21:
The Moon and Tonkatsu.
The Moon and Tonkatsu
Episode 21
You will witness the depths of sorcery.